You know, I always been
by him.
Okay. That's probably like one
of my only really solid
spots.
When reality kicks in, it's
when my son kick in.
For a second I was
in denial, like, you know
my son, you know I
always wanna be like, oh
my son's okay. It's just,
like, which is he's okay?
But
you're thinking like, what?
And it's like, yeah,
your son
is autistic.
So,
there's certain things I gotta
go through.
There's certain reasons why I
ask myself, like, why? Like
me.
Maybe he
chose you. Maybe you were
the perfect father for him.
Maybe he needed somebody sensitive
and caring and had the
means of taking care of
him because he'll need somebody
to take care of him
his entire life. Yeah.
So maybe you are the
father that's been honored for
that special child, that special
child that has special needs.
Yeah.
Right.